linkdelight.com 2019-03-02

# Security & Privacy | Security and Privocy

**Data Security**

The security of your personal information is very important to us. In an effort to protect your personal information, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with 256 bit encryption. If your browser supports SSL (most current browsers do), it will automatically encrypt the information you provide to us on the secure pages on our site, before sending it over the Internet.

When visiting a page on our site that includes any of your personal information, the bottom of your browser window will display, an icon of a closed lock or an unbroken key (depending upon your browser). This indicates that you have successfully connected with our secure server.

To authenticate the security of your connection before submitting any of your personal information, you can double click on the icon to display our digital certificate.

Some browser versions and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, we suggest that you contact us by phone, or fax your order to us.

**What information do we collect and store?**

Registered email/ password /nickname/ IP address/ the date and time/ browser and operating system/ the URL you requested/ your PayPal email / your PayPal shipping address and other information. Some examples of why we need this information include assisting in pre orders, delivery, payment verification, promotions and newsletters, statistics on website use to aid in improving our customer experience and offering the most popular products. To contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have elected not to receive promotional communications in connection with this website. If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link.

 **Note:** No one other than yourself can access your password, including our staff.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not.

Our website uses cookies for the purpose of 'remembering' customers' choice of local site only.

**News Letter**

Customers may opt-in and opt-out of our newsletter service. Our newsletter subscription service application may collect customer's demographic data in order to provide suitable content to subscribers. Customers may opt-out of the newsletter at anytime. Instructions on how to opt-out come with every newsletter sent.

**Links**

Our web site contains links to other web sites that are not operated by linkdelight.com. linkdelight.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate. Some parts of the Web site are animated using various downloadable applications, such as Macromedia’s Shockwave/Flash.

 **Questions or Concerns**

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu. Or through the following methods:

Tel: +86-13692245940

Email: [info@linkdelight.com](mailto:info@linkdelight.com) .

Contact Address:

Linkdelight Limited 5F, Building 9, Bagualing Industrial Estate, No.2  
Bagua Road, 518029, Shenzhen, PRC China 

Phone:+86-13692245940(Office time: 9:00am to 6:00pm GMT + 08:00.  on Monday through Saturday)
